(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T16:30:20.613469",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
みんなーAZKi！
Everyone, it's AZKi!
今日はAZKi 8th Birthday Live クロスオーバー 平成令和アニソン歌合戦にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to AZKi's 8th Birthday Live Crossover: Heisei vs Reiwa Anime Song Battle!
今回は平成赤チームと令和青チームの2チームに分かれてアニソン歌合戦を行っていきます！
This time, we're splitting into two teams—the Heisei Red Team and the Reiwa Blue Team—for an anime song battle!
今回ゲストの皆もそれぞれのねチームに分かれて参戦してくれます！
Our guest performers will also be joining and competing across both teams!
ハッシュタグは「AZKi生誕ライブ2026」こちらこちら！
The hashtag is '#AZKiBirthdayLive2026', right here!
で、ぜひですね、赤チームここがよかったよとか、青チームここが美しかったよとかですね、たくさんポストお願いします！
And please post lots about how great the Red Team was here, or how beautiful the Blue Team was there!
そして、サムネイルにも書いてありますが、新衣装のお披露目と重大告知もあるので楽しみにしていてください！
And as written in the thumbnail, we'll also have a new outfit reveal and major announcements, so please look forward to it!
ということで、みんな盛り上がる準備はいいかー！
With that said, are you all ready to get hyped?!
それでは平成令和アニソン歌合戦、開会です！
Now then, let the Heisei vs Reiwa Anime Song Battle begin!
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A Cruel Angel's Thesis
One Last Kiss
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ神話になれ
young boy, become a myth.
蒼い風がいま 胸のドアを叩いても
Even if a blue wind now knocks on the door of my heart,
私だけをただ見つめて微笑んでるあなた
you just gaze at me alone and smile.
そっとふれるもの 求めることに夢中で
Lost in the desire to gently touch what we seek,
運命さえまだ知らない いたいけな瞳
innocent eyes that still know nothing of fate.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう その背中には
Yet someday you'll realize that on your back,
遥か未来めざすための羽根があること
there are wings to aim for a distant future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis will soon take flight from the window,
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
if with gushing, burning pathos you betray your memories.
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
Embracing this universe, shine bright, young boy, become a myth.
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a myth.
ずっと眠ってる 私の愛の揺りかご
Sleeping endlessly in my cradle of love,
あなただけが 夢の使者に 呼ばれる朝がくる
the morning comes when only you are called as a messenger of dreams.
細い首筋を 月あかりが映してる
Moonlight reflects upon the nape of your slender neck.
世界中の時を止めて 閉じ込めたいけど
I want to stop time across the world and lock it away, but...
もしもしふたり逢えたことに 意味があるなら
If there's a meaning to the two of us meeting,
私はそう 自由を知るためのバイブル
I am, yes, the bible to know freedom.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみがそしてはじまる
Like a cruel angel's thesis, sadness begins.
抱きしめた命のかたち その夢に目覚めたとき
When you awaken to that dream, the shape of the life you embraced,
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ神話になれ
shining brighter than anyone else—young boy, become a myth.
人は愛をつむぎながら 歴史をつくる
People weave love as they create history.
女神なんてなれないまま 私は生きる
I live on without ever becoming a goddess.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
Like a cruel angel's thesis, you will soon take flight from the window.
ほどばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories with surging, burning pathos,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
embracing this universe and shining—young boy, become a myth.
初めてのルーブルは なんてことはなかったわ
My first time at the Louvre was no big deal,
私だけのモナリザ もうとっくに出会ってたから
because I'd already met my own Mona Lisa long ago.
初めてあなたを見た あの日動き出した歯車
The day I first laid eyes on you, the gears started turning.
止められない喪失の予感
An unstoppable premonition of loss.
もういっぱいあるけど
We already have so many, but
もう一つ増やしましょう
let's add another one.
(Can you give me one last kiss?)
忘れたくなくて
I don't want to forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
「写真は苦手なんだ」 でもそんなものはいらないわ
"I don't like being photographed," but I don't need such things.
あなたが焼きついたまま 私の心のプロジェクター
Your image is burnt forever on my heart's projector.
寂しくないふりしてた まあ、そんなのお互い様か
I was pretending not to be lonely—well, I guess we're even.
誰かを求めることは 即ち傷つくことだった
Yearning for someone was synonymous with getting hurt.
Oh, can you give me one last kiss?
燃えるようなキスをしよう
Let's share a kiss as hot as fire.
忘れたくても
Even if I want to forget,
忘れられないほど
so much that I can't forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
Oh oh oh oh…
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
もう分かっているよ この世の終わりでも
I already know, even at the end of this world
年をとっても
Even as we grow old
忘れられない人
You're an unforgettable person
Oh oh oh oh…
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
忘れられない人
An unforgettable person
I love you more than you'll ever know
忘れられない人
You're an unforgettable person
I love you more than you'll ever know
吹いていった 風の後を
Following the wind that blew past
追いかけた 眩しい午後
I chased after that dazzling afternoon
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover
平成赤チーム 常闇トワ
Heisei Red Team: Tokoyami Towa
Don't say "lazy"
続いて令和青チーム 響咲リオナ
Continuing with Reiwa Blue Team: Hibiki Riona
星座になれたら
"If I Could Be a Constellation"
2曲続けてどうぞ！
Two songs in a row, here we go!
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当はcrazy
Please don't say "You are lazy" 'cause it'll drive me crazy
白鳥たちはそう 見えないところでバタ足するんです
Graceful swans thrash their wings where nobody sees
本能に順従 充実 翻弄も重々承知
True to our instincts, well aware we're being toyed with
前途洋々だし… だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
Our future's bright... so we take a break once in a while
この目でしっかり見定め 行き先地図上マークして
With my own eyes I'll find my destination and map it out
近道あればそれが王道 はしゃげる翼があれば上等
If there's a shortcut it's the royal road, wings to soar are a bonus
ヤバ爪割れた グールで補修した それだけでなんか達成感
Oh crap, broke a nail, fixed it with glue, feeling satisfied
大事なのは自分 かわいがること
The most important thing is to cherish yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
You can't love others if you don't love yourself
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当はcrazy
Please don't say "You are lazy" 'cause it'll drive me crazy
能ある鷹はそう 見えないところにピック隠すんです
Talented hawks hide their picks where no one can see
想像に一生懸命 現実絶体絶命 発展途中だし…
Trying hard in imagination, facing doom in reality, still growing...
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
That's why my pitch suddenly goes off!
その目に映らないだけだってやる気はメーター振り切って
It's just out of sight, my motivation is maxed out!
いつでも全力で夢見てその分全力で眠って
Dreaming with all my heart, sleeping just as hard!
ヤリ ちい痩せた 調子づいて喰った
Yeah, I lost a bit of weight, got cocky and pigged out—
それだけでなんで? 敗北感
and why does that feel like defeat?
すかさず目標下方修正して
Quickly revising my goals downward,
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
being flexible and adapting wins the game!
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当はcrazy
Please don't say "You are lazy" 'Cause it's really crazy!
孔雀たちはそう ここぞというとき美を魅せるんです
Peacocks, you see, show their beauty when it counts!
五臓六腑 満身 邁進 願望は復讐 麗人
Body and soul, charging forward, desire disguised as elegance!
誘惑多発だし… だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
Temptations are everywhere... so my willpower easily shatters!
ヤバ まさか赤点!? いやギリクリア!
Oh no, failing grade?! No, barely cleared!
それだけでなんて全能感
Just that gives me such a sense of omnipotence!
大事なのは自分 認めてくこと
The important thing is accepting yourself,
自分を許さなきゃ 他人も許せない
if you can't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others.
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当はcrazy
Please don't say "You are lazy" 'Cause it's really crazy!
白鳥たちはそう 見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Swans, you see, paddle frantically where you can't see!
本能に順応 充実 煩悩も従順 熟知
Adapting to instincts, fulfilling desires, knowing them well!
前途洋々だし… だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
The future is bright... so sometimes I take a break!
もうすぐ時計は6時
It's almost 6 o'clock.
もうそこに一番星
The first star is already right there.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
Stepping on my shadow, walking home, wanting to blend into the night.
どんなに探してみても
No matter how much I search,
一つしかない星
there's only one star.
何億光年 離れたところからあんなに輝く
Shining so brightly from hundreds of millions of light-years away.
いいな 君は みんなから愛されて
Must be nice, being loved by everyone.
「いいや 僕は ずっと一人きりさ」
"Not really, I've always been all alone."
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
on a starry night, my fleeting wish...
きらめいて ゆらめいて 震えてるシグナル
Shimmering, swaying, a trembling signal.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation...
空見上げて 指を差せるような
Looking up at the sky, like pointing fingers at it,
つないだ線 解かないで
Don't untie the line that connects us!
僕がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how blindingly you shine...
もうすぐ時計は8時
It's almost 8 o'clock.
夜空に満天の星
The night sky is full of stars.
何億光年 離れたところにはもうないかもしれない
Billions of light years away, they might not even be there anymore.
月が綺麗で
The moon is so beautiful,
泣きそうになるのは
it makes me want to cry,
いつの日か 別れが来るから
because someday a farewell will come.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If we gather together and become a constellation,
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
like a shooting star, each straying alone,
消えていく 残像は 真夜中のプリズム
the fading afterimage is a midnight prism.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If we gather together and become a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
if my heartbreaking wish reaches someone,
変われるかな 夜の淵を
can the edge of the night change?
なぞるような こんな僕でも
Even a me who just traces it like this...
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far away, we happened to meet each other.
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
It's karma, so we'll meet again and again.
雲の隙間で
Through the gaps in the clouds,
君と集まって星座になれたら
if we gather together and become a constellation,
夜広げて 描こう絵空事を
let's spread the night and paint our imaginary dream.
暗闇を照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if it's not a full moon to light the darkness,
だから集まって星座になりたい
that's why I want to gather and be a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような
releasing lights of various colors.
つないだ線 解かないよ
Don't untie the line that connects us,
君がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how blindingly you shine.
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
I can hear you wherever you are.
君がくれる Agape
The Agape you give me,
力の限り Dive!
Dive with all your might!
みつめる 触れ合う その時
The moment we gaze and touch each other,
愛は二人を試している
love is putting the two of us to the test.
Time is now...
この世の果てまで
To the end of this world...
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it,
君がくれる Agape
the Agape you give me.
力の限り Dive!
Dive with all your might!
信じる 応える その瞬間
The moment we believe and respond,
愛が 僕らを ひとつにする
love makes us one.
Time is now... Time is now...
どこまでも生きて
Living on, no matter how far...
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it,
君がくれる Agape
the Agape you give me.
力の限り Dive!
Dive with all your might!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it,
君がくれる Agape
the Agape you give me.
力の限り Dive!
Dive with all your might!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it,
君がくれる Agape
the Agape you give me.
力の限り Dive!
Dive with all your might!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it,
君がくれる Agape
the Agape you give me.
力の限り Dive!
Dive with all your might!
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中！
Radio tempo up, electrifying right now!
あなたにも忘れたいことかないこと あるのかしらね
I wonder if there are things you want to forget, too.
知らない映画なのに涙をながすのはドラマチックが足りてないからよ
Crying at an unknown movie means there's not enough drama.
そんな愚にも付かないことくだらないこと考えてばかりね
You're always thinking about such silly, pointless things.
雨が上がれば愛もその横顔も誰かのものになるのでしょう
When the rain stops, love and that profile will belong to someone else.
嘘っぱちのファンデーションも全部
All the fake foundations...
今夜のためよ
are for tonight.
なのに一体全体如何して如何して何故何故？
But why on earth, why, why?
不安定なカンテラ何処まで行くの
How far will this unstable lantern go?
あなた一切合切放り去ってもう
You've left everything behind and gone.
冗談じゃないないわ
I'm not joking around!
トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来だって如何にもなんないぜ
Even when that time comes, nothing can be done.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths only make me melancholic.
あたしをさあ掠奪て今テイクオンミー
So snatch me away and take me on now!
ちゃんちゃらおかしな法度ばっかで食指がびくともしないわ
Strange laws abound, and my appetite won't budge at all.
実態の無い感情放っておいたって策略なんてありゃあせんのに何故
Why, when I leave substance-less emotions alone, are there no strategies?
ああもう懲り懲りよ あたしの喝となる気質もじっと堪えて取り繕ってはとうとう臨界点
Ah, I've had enough. My strict nature has endured and kept up appearances until it reached a critical point.
年から年中リップサービス鈍感かましては平気いき
All year round lip service, acting insensitive without a care.
どんがらがっしゃんフィールガールは涙の目にも鬼
Clattering, crashing feel girls are merciless even with teary eyes.
今や頭の中のミュージックのせいであなたの話は一向に聴き取れない
Now, because of the music in my head, I can't hear a word you're saying at all.
少しは真当なこと言って
Say something sensible for once!
回り出すターンテーブル ねぇ全部忘れさせてよ
The turntable starts spinning, hey, let me forget everything.
だけど一体全体如何して如何して何故何故？
But why on earth, why, why?
不安定なカンテラ消えないままね
The unstable lantern still won't go out.
あなた一口両舌食い違ってもう
You speak with a forked tongue and our stories don't match.
冗談じゃないないわ
I'm not joking around!
トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来だって如何にもなんないぜ
Even when that time comes, nothing can be done.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths only make me melancholic.
あたしを今...
Snatch me right now...
冗談じゃないないわ
I'm not joking around!
トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来だって如何にもなんないぜ
Even when that time comes, nothing can be done.
不甲斐ないわ
How pathetic.
感情なんてランドリーで落とすだけ
I just wash away my emotions in the laundry.
あたしと確かめ合ってイエローマジック
Confirming yellow magic with me.
トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来だって如何にもなんないぜ
Even when that time comes, nothing can be done.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths only make me melancholic.
あたしをさあ掠奪て今テイクオンミー
So snatch me away and take me on now!
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover 平和 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover Heisei vs. Reiwa Anison Battle
最後はチームみんなで歌い上げます
Finally, both teams will sing together!
平成 赤チーム
Heisei Red Team
アニメ「とある科学の超電磁砲」より未だ愛され続けるアニソンの王道「only my railgun」
From the anime A Certain Scientific Railgun, the timeless anime song classic: "only my railgun"
続いて 令和 青チーム
Next, Reiwa Blue Team
アニメ「呪術廻戦」より鮮烈でエモーショナルな青春ソング「青のすみか」
From the anime Jujutsu Kaisen, the vivid and emotional youth song: "Where Our Blue Is"
ステージでぶつかる電撃と磁力 2曲続けてどうぞ
Electric shocks and magnetic force collide on stage! Enjoy two songs back-to-back.
放て！心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Fire away! Leave behind the future and the dreams engraved in your heart.
限界など知らない 意味無い
It knows no limits and has no meaning.
この能力が光放す その先に遥かな想いを
My power will radiate these distant feelings.
歩いてきた この道を 振り返ることでしか
If I can only look back on this path that I tried to walk,
出来ないなら…今ここで全てを壊せる
I could destroy it all here and now.
暗闇に堕ちる街並み 人はどこまで立ち向かえるの？
The streets descend into darkness. How far will people go to resist?
加速するその痛みから 誰かをきっと守れるよ
I'm sure I'll be able to protect someone from this worsening pain.
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it now.
身体中を 光の速さで
At the speed of light through my body,
駆け巡った 確かな予感
A certain premonition rushed through.
掴め! 望むものなら残さず
Catch it! If it's your wish, leave nothing behind,
輝ける自分らしさで
With your shining true self.
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを
I believe in the vow of that day,
この瞳に光る涙 それさえも
The tears shining in these eyes, even those
強さに なるから
Will become my strength.
立ち止まると 少しだけ
Standing still, I feel just a bit
感じる切なさに
Of this sudden sorrow,
戸惑う事 無いなんて
To say I have no doubts
嘘はつかないよ
Would be a lie.
宇宙に舞うコインが描く
The coin dancing in space draws
放物線が決める運命
A parabolic arc that decides our fate.
打ち出した答えが今日も
The conclusion I fired off today, too,
私の胸を駆け巡る
Rushes through my chest.
Sparkling! The shiny lights awake true desire
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it 必ず
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it for sure.
貫いてく 迷うことなく
Piercing through without hesitation,
傷ついても 走り続ける
Even if I'm hurt, I'll keep running on.
狙え! 凛と煌く視線は
Aim! My cold, sparkling gaze
狂い無く闇を切り裂く
Tears through the darkness without a flaw.
迷いなんて 吹き飛ばせばいい
Blow away any hesitation,
この心が叫ぶ限り
As long as this heart is shouting,
誰ひとり邪魔などさせない
I won't let anyone stand in my way.
儚く舞う 無数の願いは
Countless fleeting wishes dancing about
この両手にいつも持ってゆく
I will always hold in both hands.
切り裂く闇に見えてくるのは
What comes into view in the tearing darkness
重く深く 切ない記憶
Are heavy, deep, and painful memories.
色褪せてく 現実に揺れる
Trembling in a fading reality,
絶望には負けたくない
I don't want to lose to despair.
私が今 私であること
That I am myself right now,
胸を張って 全て誇れる!
I can proudly hold my head high!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it 今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it right now.
身体中を 光の速さで
At the speed of light through my body,
駆け巡った 確かな予感
A certain premonition rushed through.
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を
Release the dreams engraved in your heart,
未来さえ置き去りにして
Leaving even the future behind.
限界など知らない 意味無い!
Knowing no limits, it's meaningless!
この能力が光放す
The light emitted by this power—
その先に遥かな想いを
Far beyond it lies my distant feelings.
どこまでも 続くような
In the endless blue season
青の季節は
That seems to go on forever,
四つ並ぶ 眼の前を
Four lined-up eyes before us
遮るものは 何もない
Have nothing blocking their way.
アスファルト
Asphalt
蝉時雨を 反射して
Reflects the cicadas' rain,
君という沈黙が
And the silence that is you
聞こえなくなる
Becomes inaudible.
この日々が 色褪せる
These days fade away in color,
僕と違う 君の匂いを知ってしまっても
Even though I've come to know your scent, different from mine.
置き忘れてきた
Left behind at the bottom
永遠の底に
Of eternity.
今でも青は 澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear,
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも 言葉も
Though every prayer and word
近づけるのに、届かなかった
Came close, they didn't reach you.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Like a quiet romance,
頬を伝った 夏のような色の中
Within colors like summer running down my cheek.
君を呪う言葉が
Words cursing you
ずっと喉の奥につかえてる
Stay caught deep in my throat.
「また会えるよね」って 声にならない声
"We'll meet again," a voice that cannot become a voice.
昼下がり、じめつく風の季節は
In the afternoon, in the humid, sticky wind's season,
想い馳せる、まだ何者でもなかった僕らの肖像
I let my thoughts wander, our portrait when we were still nobody.
何もかも分かち合えたはずだった
We should have been able to share everything.
あの日から少しずつ、君と違うという呪いが肥っていく
Since that day, bit by bit, the curse of being different from you has grown.
きみの笑顔の奥の憂いを
The sadness deep within your smile,
見落としたこと、悔やみ尽くして
I regret overlooking it, regretting it to the end.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君に
To you, who bloom in vain and scatter,
さよなら
Goodbye.
今でも青が滲んでいる
Even now, blue is bleeding through.
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も
No matter what prayer or words,
近づけるのに、届かなかった
They came close, but didn't reach.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Like a quiet love,
頬を伝った夏のような色のなか
In the midst of summer-like colors running down my cheeks,
きみを呪う言葉がずっと喉の奥につかえてる
The words to curse you are forever stuck in the back of my throat.
「また会えるよね」って、声にならない声
"We'll meet again," a voiceless voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のように
Like the star particles of an infinitely expanding galaxy,
指の隙間を零れた
They spilled through the gaps between my fingers.
はい、ということで、ここまで一気にノンストップでお送りしました！
Yes, and with that, we've delivered all of that nonstop so far!
いや平成も令和も、名曲ばかりでしたね！
Man, Heisei and Reiwa, they were all such masterpieces!
どうでしたか？好きな曲はありましたか？
How was it? Were there any songs you liked?
そして、みんなどっちのチームが良かったかな？
And which team do you all think did best?
ええとですね、この、このね今後ろのこのハートのステージね
Umm, so, this, this heart stage behind me here,
はい、こちらのハートに映し出された色でどっちのチームが勝ったか決まります！
Yes, the color projected onto this heart will decide which team won!
ぜひ、みんなコメントでどっちが良かったか教えてください！
Please let us know in the comments which one was better!
えー！決められない？
Eh?! You can't decide?
いやいやそこはね、ちょっとね決めて、あの、この2色にね、分かれておりますけれども
No, no, you gotta decide, um, it's split into these two colors, but...
今日はね、あの平成VS令和となっております
Today is, um, Heisei versus Reiwa.
はい、ということで、勝ったのは平成赤チームか、それとも令和青チームか！いったいどっちかな？
Yes, and with that, did the Heisei Red Team win, or the Reiwa Blue Team? Which one could it be?
それじゃあ行くよ！さあ、結果は…こちら！
Well then, here we go! Now, the result is... right here!
えっ？なんか紫になっちゃったんですけど！
Huh? Somehow it turned purple!
紫って、紫ってどっちですか？
Purple? Which one is purple?
うーん、もうこれは、あの赤チームもよかったし青チームもよかったということで、すべてフュージョンして紫になってしまった！
Um, well, since both the Red Team and Blue Team were great, they all fused and turned purple!
というわけで、いやみんな、あの、たくさん歌ったし、みんな最高だったってことにね、します！ね、します！
So, um, everyone sang a lot, and everyone was the best—let's make it that! Yeah, let's!
いやなんか、いやなんかさ、みんなのおかげで、あ、なんかパワーが、パワーがたまってきた気がするな！
Man, like, thanks to everyone, I feel like, oh, energy, energy has built up!
ということで、新曲でーす！
And with that, it's a new song!
ネットが全部亜希の魔力になっちゃった。
The internet has completely become AZKi's magic!
見てください。どうですか？
Look at this. How is it?
尻尾も、尻尾も生えてるんです。ふりふりふりふり。どうですか？
I even have a tail! Wiggle wiggle wiggle... What do you think?
はい。ということで今回は、小悪魔衣装をおしたていただきました。
Yes. So this time, I had a little devil outfit custom-made!
どうでしょうか？どうでしょうか？魔力、魔王、小悪魔です。はい。
How is it? How is it? Magic, demon king, little devil. Yes.
今回ですね、新衣装はこちらの小悪魔衣装。可愛いでしょう？たくさんスクショ撮ってくださいね。
This time, the new outfit is this little devil costume. Cute, right? Please take lots of screenshots!
ということで、この衣装でね、せっかくなので、アニソンを歌っていきたいなと思います。
So, since it's this special outfit, I'd like to sing an anime song!
いや、もしかしたらね、小悪魔ですから、この姿なら魔法とかも使えちゃうんじゃないのかな？
If anything, since I'm a little devil, maybe with this look, I can even use magic and stuff?
ということで、ではですね、次の曲、聞いてください。
So now, please listen to the next song.
自分の過去に囚われ迷って
Trapped by my own past and lost within it,
そうじゃないよと言い聞かせて全てを
Telling myself, "That's not how it is,"
自由に操れるかなんて
Wondering if I can freely control it all,
分からないよと空は霞んで正解はどこ？
Saying "I don't know" as the sky grows hazy — where is the correct answer?
僕の手のひらに 残る大事なもの
The important thing remaining in the palm of my hand,
忘れない記憶 何度でも
The unforgettable memory, no matter how many times,
君を守り抜くと叫んで
Shouting that I will protect you through to the end.
巻き戻しの中 掴んだ愛はそう
The love I grabbed onto amidst the rewinding of time — yes,
離しはしないから
Because I will never let it go,
散りばめた想い 今度きりの願いへ
The scattered thoughts, now toward this one-time-only wish,
次への僕に 託したよ
I have entrusted it to the next version of myself.
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
The promise from someday will become a guidepost of light.
誓いをさあ君のため 最期まで
Now, for your sake, I swear an oath until the very end.
涙さえ力に変えてきっと 描いていた望み未来へ 繋ぐよ
Turning even tears into strength, surely connecting to the desired future I had envisioned.
想像を超える事態に狂って
Driven mad by a situation that exceeds imagination,
爪を立ててはもがき足掻いて心は
Digging in my claws, tossing and turning, struggling, my heart —
人生の過ちをもう何回 繰り返しては嫌いになって
Just how many times has it repeated the mistakes of life, growing to hate myself and crying,
泣いてても
crying even when...
君の憧れは いつも輝いていた
Your longing was always shining brightly.
I'll come back... To your future
僕は抗うだろう 運命に
I will resist, against fate.
Breaking out... 諦めないから
Breaking out... I will not give up.
結ばれた意志は 独りきりじゃない強さへ
The bound will becomes a strength that is not alone,
紡いだ糸を手繰り寄せ
I pull the spun threads closer,
見つけた瞳は理想を現実にかえる
The gaze I found changes ideal into reality.
世界はそう君のため 最初から 胸に抱いた思い出とずっと あの日から続く決意で
The world is, yes, for your sake from the beginning, with the memories held in my heart and determination continuing from that day.
飛べるよ Redo
I can fly, Redo.
君がたとえ僕のことを忘れても
Even if you forget about me,
僕はもう忘れない 誰も傷つけない 消えそうな過去を救い出すための時間よ
I won't forget anymore, I won't hurt anyone, oh time, meant for rescuing the past that seems about to vanish.
ここから始め
Start from here.
始まり
Begin.
巡りゆく一瞬を 今度きりの願いへ
Turning the fleeting moments into this one-time-only wish,
確かには僕は 託された
I was certainly entrusted with it,
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
The promise from someday will become a guidepost of light.
誓いをさあ君のため 最期まで
Now, for your sake, I swear an oath until the very end.
涙さえ力に変えてきっと 描いていた望む未来へ
Turning even tears into strength, connecting to the desired future I envisioned.
繋ぐよ
I will connect it.
ということで来ていただいてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
今日はこっくんも一緒になって魔法で召喚しちゃいました！
Today, I used magic to summon Kokon along with me!
召喚されちゃいました！こんあずき！
I got summoned! Kon-AZKi!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
ということでね皆さんもご存知だとは思うんですが、アニソン界のエース鈴木このみさんに異世界転生してもらいました！
As you all know, we had Konomi Suzuki, the ace of the anisong world, reincarnate into another world!
召喚されました！こんあずき！
I've been summoned! Kon-AZKi!
誕生日はね、今日はお祝いしたいなと思って...
Since today is your birthday, I wanted to celebrate...
参りました！ありがとうございます！
So I came! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ということでですね、一緒に歌った曲は、リゼロから始める異世界生活のファーストシーズンオープニングテーマ「Redo」でした！
So, the song we sang together was "Redo", the first season opening theme of "Re:ZERO"!
いかがでしたか？ドキドキしたなー。
How was it? My heart was pounding so much.
いや私もめっちゃドキドキした。
Yeah, my heart was pounding like crazy too.
「Redo」をひとと歌ったことがあんまりなくて...
I haven't really sung "Redo" with someone else before...
すごく恐い顔をして歌ってないかすごい心配です。
So I was really worried if I was singing with a scary face.
貴重な貴重な経験ありがとうございます。あずきちと歌えて楽しかった！
Thank you for such a precious experience. It was so fun singing with Azukichi!
あずきちって呼んでくれてるんですよ、みんな。
Everyone calls me Azukichi, you know.
あずきはね、このみんって呼んでるんですけど。
And Azki calls her Konomi-min.
いやその出会いのきっかけはですね...
Well, the catalyst for how we met was...
いやもうずっとあずきはもともと大好きなんですけど、
Well, I've always loved Azki from the start, but...
このみがね、あの、「異世界カルテット」の...
Konomi... for "Isekai Quartet"...
そうそう！異世界カルテット3のエンディングテーマ、キミイロボク色のカルテットバージョンを作ることに...なりまして！
That's right! We were going to make a quartet version of "Kimiiro Boku-iro", the ending theme for "Isekai Quartet 3"!
でその時に、あの、会社の人から...
And at that time, someone from the company said...
「誰か一人好きな人を召喚できる権利を差し上げます」って言われて、
"We'll grant you the right to summon one person you like."
「そんな機会あるなら、あずきちにお願いしてみたい」って、私ライブももと見てたんで。
I thought, "If there's such a chance, I'd love to ask Azukichi." I'd always been watching your lives, you see.
いつかコラボしたいなっていう気持ちがずっとあったので...
I'd always had this feeling of wanting to collaborate someday...
そこてラブコールをして、叶いまして！
So I sent a love call, and it came true!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! Thank you!
そんなことがありまして、そこから、あのコラボ配信とか、あのあずきもね、あの、このみのライブ見に行かせてもらったりとか...
So that happened, and since then we've done collab streams, and Azki went to see Konomi's live show...
ありがとー！
Thank you!
あとはね、ラーメンの...ラーメンの汁をね！飛ばしました！
And also, ramen... ramen broth! I spilled it!
あの、配信の日にそういう話をしていて、あの、すぐLINEを交換して、すぐラーメンの汁を飛ばして...
We talked about that on the stream day, exchanged LINE right away, and right after I spilled ramen broth...
で、すぐそのあと焼肉にも行って、そう油を飛ばし...飛ばして...
And then right after that we went to yakiniku, and spilled oil... spilled it...
アフタヌーンティーにも行きました。そうそう意外とおしゃれなこともしたし、結構ね...
We also went to afternoon tea. That's right, we did unexpectedly stylish things, and lately...
そうなんです。よく会ってるよね最近。なんとなかよくさせていただいております！
That's right. We've been meeting up a lot lately. We've gotten to be really good friends!
濃厚な付き合いをさせてもらってまして、なんと今日ついにバーチャル空間に来てくれましたー！
We've had a deep relationship, and today she finally came to the virtual space!
初めてです！ありがとう！なんて楽しい空間なんだ！嬉しすぎる！
It's my first time! Thank you! What a fun space! I'm so happy!
嬉しい！なんかこの空間は魔法が使えって聞いたんですけど本当ですか？
I'm so happy! I heard we can use magic in this space, is that true?
使っちゃいますか？このみんは一体どんな魔法を？私もせっかちながら、一つだけ魔法を覚えてきたんですよ。なんとこの日のために...これだけ使える。
Shall we use it? What kind of magic does Konomi-min have? Even I, impatient as I am, learned one magic spell for this day. This is the only one I can use.
あの、これはでも、みんなと一緒じゃないと完成しない魔法なので、ぜひあずきちへの愛を込めて、一緒に歌って魔法を完成させてください！せーの！
Well, this magic won't complete unless we're all together, so please put your love for Azukichi... Sing along together and complete the magic! Ready, set!
Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday dear AZKiち、ありがとうございまーす！
Happy Birthday dear AZKi-chi, thank you so much!
Happy Birthday to you
AZKiち仕上げをお願いします！仕上げ！はい！
AZKi-chi, please do the finishing touch! The finish! Yes!
このみんは炎の使い手でした！おめでとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Konomi-min is a flame user! Congratulations! Thank you so much!
まさか歌までプレゼントしていただけるなんて、もうもうここで命尽きて...
To receive even a song as a present... I could even give my life right here...
だめです命尽きちゃダメなんです！あの、実はみなさん、今日重大告知と...
No, you mustn't give up your life! Actually everyone, today we have a major announcement...
書いてあると思うんですけどね サムネに
It's probably written on the thumbnail,
二人から重大告知がございまーす！
we have a major announcement from the two of us!
やった！なんと！
Yay! Amazingly,
二人のオリジナルコラボ楽曲が出まーす！
our original collaboration song is coming out!
やったー！うれしい！えー！
Yay! I'm so happy! Eh?
いいんですか？いいんですか？
Is this okay? Is it really okay?
ということでタイトルは、せーの、「最強未来衝動」！
So, the title is—ready, set—"Saikyo Mirai Shodo"!
と いう なんだか強そうなタイトルですね。
That's a rather powerful-sounding title.
強い曲ですね。強い曲です。
It's a powerful song. A very powerful song.
ということでなんと今日初披露させていただきます！
And so, we're going to perform it live for the first time today!
がんばろう！
Let's do our best!
それでは早速聴いてもらえますか？
Now, would you listen to it right away?
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
それでは聴いてください！
Now then, please listen!
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR もっと WOW WOW
So, JUST FLY TO THE STAR, even more, WOW WOW,
世界中で PROUDY GLOW
PROUDY GLOW all over the world.
存在など決り切ってないない
Existence isn't fully decided,
壊れても関係ない
it doesn't matter even if it breaks.
そっと触れるよ 生まれたての星へ
Gently touching, to a newborn star,
囁きながら 願い重ねた宇宙
whispering while stacking wishes upon the cosmos.
ほどけた軌道は 誰も知らない場所へ
The unraveled orbit heads to an unknown place.
微かな記憶と夢を この声に込めて
Putting faint memories and dreams into this voice,
今を 過去を 未来を 辿る
tracing the present, the past, and the future.
一瞬を 一生を この手で掴む超 BIG ! BANG !
Grasping a moment, a whole lifetime with these hands, super BIG ! BANG !
ただこのまま果てまで溶けちゃって
Just dissolving all the way to the end as it is,
切り裂かれたような衝動
an impulse like being torn apart.
抱かれて染まって振り切って
Embraced, stained, pushing past the limit,
まだまだほら星を締め付ける
still, look, tightening the grip on the stars.
君と絡まってみようか
Shall I intertwine with you?
止まらないよ最強未来衝動
It won't stop, our ultimate future impulse!
剥がれ落ちてく
Peeling and falling off,
広がって 咲いて 駆け出して 飛んで
spreading, blooming, running out, and flying—
君と JUST FLY TO THE STAR もっと WOW WOW
You and JUST FLY TO THE STAR, even more, WOW WOW,
無重力で DREAMY SHOW
DREAMY SHOW in zero gravity.
運命など待ち切れないない
We can't wait for fate,
壊れても関係ない
it doesn't matter even if it breaks.
そっと祈るよ 幾千年の星へ
Praying gently to the stars of millennia,
彷徨いながら 僕ら出会えたんだ
wandering, we finally met.
燃え尽きる前に 誰れも彼も急ぐよ
Before burning out, everyone rushes on.
確かな希望と信念を この声に込めて
Putting sure hope and belief into this voice,
星よ光れ 闇を照らせ
Shine, oh stars, illuminate the darkness,
歌よ響け 遥か彼方へ SHOW BIG ! BANG !
sing, oh song, far into the distance, SHOW BIG ! BANG !
引力にさ 導かれ
Guided by gravity,
この手を繋いだら それだけでいい
if we hold hands, that's all we need.
聞いて！鳴り止ない絶唱
Listen! An unending death song,
愛して焦がして振り切って
loving, yearning, pushing past the limit,
まだまだほらそれを駆け巡る
still, look, running around through it all.
君を狂わせてみようか
Shall I drive you mad?
止まらないで絶対未来衝動
Don't stop, absolute future impulse!
生まれ落ちてく
Being born and falling down,
そばにいて 触れて 輝いて 消えて
stay by my side, touch me, shine, and vanish.
生きることは 銀河を旅する STORY
Living is a STORY of journeying through the galaxy.
どこまでも走っていく どこまでも燃やしていく
Running on endlessly, burning on endlessly,
どこまでも生命がある限り 叫べ
as long as there is life anywhere, shout out!
伝えたい この淡い衝動
I want to convey this faint impulse...
伝えたい この熱い衝動を
I want to convey this burning impulse
ここから 次元を超えていく
transcending dimensions from right here.
超えていく 超えていく
Transcending... transcending...
歌え！この衝動は きっと
Sing! This impulse will surely
抱かれて 染まって 振り切って まだ まだ
embrace, dye, and shake it off, still, still—
ほら また 星を 締め付ける
Look, once again it constricts the stars.
君と絡まってみようか
Shall I intertwine with you?
止まらないよ 最強未来衝動 ただ ただ
It won't stop, the ultimate future impulse, just... just...
剥がれ落ちていく
peeling and falling away.
広がって 避けて 駆け出して 飛んで
Spreading, avoiding, breaking out, and flying—
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR もっと WOW WOW
So JUST FLY TO THE STAR, even more WOW WOW!
世界中で PROUDLY GLOW 存在など 抱き切って無い無い
PROUDLY GLOW worldwide, not holding back any existence at all!
壊れても 関係ない
It doesn't matter even if it breaks!
はーい、ということで、新曲を披露させていただきましたー！
Hii! So, we just unveiled our new song!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
かっこいい曲になりましたね、このみ。
It turned out to be such a cool song, Konomi.
映え曲！
A banger!
映え曲！映え曲！
A banger! A banger!
ということでですね、「最強未来衝動」、本日この後7月2日0時からデジタルリリースされますー！
So, "Saikyou Mirai Shoudou" will be digitally released
today, starting at midnight on July 2nd!
ちょっと、せっかくなんでに、この曲、実は二人ね、二人で歌詞を そうなんです。
Since we have the chance, this song... actually,
the two of us wrote the lyrics together. That's right.
一緒に歌詞を作らせていただいて、二日間、一緒に缶詰の状態で
We worked on the lyrics together and spent
two days locked up in a room together—
一緒に缶詰になって部屋にね、閉じこもって、このみんと一緒に、あの、作詞をするという
locked in a room together with Konomi,
doing the songwriting,
貴重な、大変貴重な、経験をさせていただきました。
which was such a precious,
incredibly precious experience.
いや、私も、なんかすごい、あの、楽しかったし、こう、中も深まったんじゃないかっていう
Yeah, I also felt like it was super fun
and that our bond deepened even more.
そう、中も深まったんじゃないかって気がしております。
Yes, I feel like our bond grew stronger.
嬉しいです。はい、そんな楽曲ですので、ぜひぜひ隅々まで聴いてほしいなって甘えます。
I'm so happy. So since it's that kind of song,
I really want everyone to listen to every corner.
お願いします。
Please do!
と言うわけで、今日はね、この世界に来てくれてありがとうございます！
So, thank you so much
for coming to this world today!
どうでしたか？どうでしたか？
How was it? How was it?
正直っていい？めっっちゃ楽しい！
Can I be honest? It was suuuper fun!
いやもうなんか、順応してる
Yeah, like, you're totally adapting!
え、そうなの。なんかね、あの、何でもほのぼのとか出せちゃうんだよね。
Eh, really? Like, you know, you can bring
out a cozy vibe or anything.
出せちゃうし。え、ちょっとさ、最後にさ、二人でこのハートマークを作りませんか？
You can bring it out. Hey, shall we make
this heart mark together at the end?
やりたい！
I want to!
じゃあ行くよ？せーのっ！
Ready? One, two!
いいんじゃないでしょうか！
That's pretty good, right?
いいね！みんな撮れた？スクリーンショットお願いしますね。
Nice! Did everyone capture it?
Please take your screenshots!
はーい、ということで、このみんと一緒にハートを作ったということで、最後にこのみんから告知などありますか？
Right, so since Konomi and I made a heart together,
Konomi, do you have any announcements?
はい！えっと、まず7月11日に、アニサマ、夏ののアニメの祭典が行われますー！
Yes! First, on July 11th, Animelo Summer Live,
the biggest summer anime festival, will take place!
そちらに出ますー！すごいすごいすごい！
I'll be appearing there! That's amazing!
フェスモードな感じで、アニソンですよね。
It's in fes-mode, with anime songs, right?
あちちな、あちちな、あの、歌で炎をバンバン出せたらいいなと、現実でも炎を出してくれます。
I hope we can pump out flames with hot songs,
and even in reality, they'll bring out the flames.
お願いします！
Please look forward to it!
あとは、私あのライブが決まってまして、11月7日土曜日に東京AGCホールにて、アニソンコレクションプラス、
Also, I have a live concert decided—on Saturday,
November 7th, at Tokyo TDC Hall,
アニソンだけを歌うライブをやります！
I will hold an all-anisong collection live!
なんですって！？
What did you say?!
だから今日、あのあずきちゃんが、あずきが、あの、今日アニソン、ずっと歌ってて、
That's why today, Azuki, today,
you've been singing anisongs all along—
そうなんだ、今日ねアニソンテーマにしたライブとなっちょります。
yeah, today's live is themed around anisongs.
ちょっとのシザーンって、ありがとうございます、思いながら。
Feeling a bit nostalgic while thinking that.
私もそんな1日を過ごそうかなと。
I think I'll spend such a day as well.
応援しています！
I'm rooting for you!
あの代表曲ばっかり流れる、そんな、行かなきゃ！是非来てほしい。
A setlist full of representative songs—
you gotta go! I definitely want you to come.
行かなきゃ！是非是非。
You gotta go! Definitely, definitely.
ということで、ぜひ、あの詳しくはアカウントをチェックしていただいて、一緒にアニソンまみれの1日を過ごしましょう！よろしくお願いします！
So please check the accounts for details,
and let's spend a day surrounded by anisongs!
めっちゃ行きたい！
I really want to go!
はい、ということで、えー残念なんですが、そろそろこのみを元の世界に戻さないと、
Right, so unfortunately, it's almost time to return
Konomi to her original world,
あにさまも、アニメコレクションもできないので。
otherwise she won't be able to do her shows.
またご飯行こう！またご飯行こう！
Let's go eat again! Let's go eat again!
行こう行こう！やった！
Let's go, let's go! Yay!
じゃあちょっとね、魔法を使って、このみを元の世界に戻したいと思います！今日はありがとうございました！
So now, using magic, I'd like to return Konomi
to her original world! Thank you for today!
ありがとうございます！おめでとう！
Thank you! Congratulations!
ありがとうーー！
Thank youuu!
消えちゃった…
She vanished...
はい、ということでですね、えーサプライズスペシャルゲスト、鈴木このみさんに来ていただきましたー！
Right, our surprise special guest,
Konomi Suzuki, came to join us!
今日のライブ、いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was today's live concert?
ボカ、本当にね、内容盛りだくさんで、そうそう、
Oh, really, there's so much content. That's right,
このね、新しい小悪魔な衣装のことをあんまり話せなかったので、
I couldn't talk much about this new little devil outfit,
このあとメイン画面でゆっくり見てもらえたらと思います。
so I hope you can take your time looking at it on the main screen later.
実は、いろんなアクセサリーやサブがあります、ということで、
Actually, there are various accessories and extras, so...
ぜひメイン画面もよろしくお願いします。そして皆様、最後にAZKiから皆に嬉しいお知らせです！
please check out the main screen too. And everyone, finally, a happy announcement from AZKi to you all!
こちらをどうぞ！
Here it is, please take a look!
傷ついた感情も進んでいくから
Even wounded emotions will keep moving forward,
そっと響く頑張れが新しい未来を感じる
softly echoing words of encouragement make me feel a new future.
怖くだって進むしかないでしょ、どこまで
Even if it's scary, we have no choice but to press on—just how far?
届くこの祈りを光ととなれもっともっと
May these prayers reach us, becoming light, more and more,
少しずつでもいい優しいという答えを
even if it's little by little, the gentle answer.
もっと、もっと、もっと、もっと
More, more, more, more...
お待たせしました！AZKiソロライブ2025 デパーチャー ブルーレイ発売決定！
Thank you for waiting! AZKi Solo Live 2025 "Departure" Blu-ray release decided!
開拓者のみんなと紡いだあのステージが何度でも見返せます。本日より受注受付が開始です。
You can rewatch that stage woven with the Pioneers as many times as you like. Pre-orders start today.
続いて告知2つ目！AZKiの歴史を彩るEP2作品の再販が本日7月1日より全国流通スタート！
Next, announcement #2! The nationwide distribution for the reissue of two EP works coloring AZKi's history starts today, July 1st!
対象タイトルは「Without U」と「Re:Creating world」です。
The target titles are "Without U" and "Re:Creating world".
最後、告知3つ目！AZKi誕生日記念2026グッズ情報！
Finally, announcement #3! AZKi Birthday Commemoration 2026 merchandise information!
今回は、お披露目された小悪魔衣装にちなんだグッズがもりだくさんです。イラストはのぶ澤おさむ先生に描いていただきました。ありがとうございます！
This time, there's plenty of merchandise themed around the newly unveiled little devil outfit. The illustrations were drawn by Osamu Nobusawa. Thank you very much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう。まずはこちら。
Now let's look at the details. First is this.
2層アクリルパネル。小悪魔衣装のキービジュアルをアクリルパネルにしました。
2-layer acrylic panel. We made the key visual of the little devil outfit into an acrylic panel.
2層になっているので立体的に見えます。スタンドガラスの神秘的な美しさと小悪魔衣装が見せるギャップをお楽しみください。
Since it has two layers, it looks three-dimensional. Please enjoy the mysterious beauty of the stained glass and the gap shown by the little devil outfit.
続いてはこちら、ランダムラバーキーホルダー。このあとの面会でも詳しく見せちゃうんですけど、今回の新衣装、実はバリエーションがいっぱいあるのでラバーキーホルダーにしてもらいました。
Next is this, random rubber keychain. I'll show it in detail during the meeting later, but since this new outfit actually has lots of variations, we had them made into rubber keychains.
キミのお気に入りはどのアズキかな？イラストはニャドラ先生に描いていただきました。
Which AZKi is your favorite? The illustrations were drawn by Nyadora-sensei.
続いてはこちら、ぬいぐるみキーホルダー小悪魔衣装ver.。こちらも小悪魔衣装バージョンとなってます。ずきまみたいなチャメッ気のある表情になっているので、ぜひ相棒として連れ歩いてください。
Next is this, plush keychain (Little Devil Outfit ver.). This is also the little devil outfit version. It has a mischievous expression like Zukima, so please take it around as your buddy.
続いてはこちら、おそろいブレスレット。小悪魔衣装をモチーフにしたデザインのブレスレットです。日常の中でさりげなく押しをお手におまとうのはもちろん、普段アクセサリーをつけない方には新衣装の再現コレクションとしてもおすすめのグッズです。
Next is this, matching bracelet. It's a bracelet designed with the little devil outfit motif. Of course, it's great for subtly wearing your oshi in daily life, and recommended as a recreation collection of the new outfit even for those who don't usually wear accessories.
続いてはこちら、ASMRボイス。ボイスタイトルは「小悪魔チャーミング」。AZKiが小悪魔っぽく魔法をかけちゃうそんなもしものお話のASMRボイスです。
Next is this, ASMR voice. The voice title is "Little Devil Charming". It's an ASMR voice of a "what if" story where AZKi casts a spell like a little devil.
そしてフルセット購入特典もございます。のぶ澤おさむ先生イラストのAZKiのタロット風カードと特典ASMRボイスです。数量限定バージョンは直筆サイン&箔押し複製メッセージ入り、通常バージョンは箔押し複製サイン&メッセージ入りです。
And there are also full set purchase bonuses. An AZKi tarot-style card illustrated by Osamu Nobusawa and bonus ASMR voice. The limited quantity version includes a handwritten signature & foil-stamped duplicate message, and the regular version includes a foil-stamped duplicate signature & message.
ということで以上嬉しいお知らせでした！
So that was all the happy announcements!
このあとはメンゲンでアンコールライブ！まだメンゲンに入っていない方もまだ間に合うのでぜひ入ってみてください。
After this is the encore live for members! For those who haven't joined membership yet, you still have time, so please check it out.
実は今回の新衣装みんなにまだ見せていないあんな姿やこんな姿があるので見に来てくれたら嬉しいです。
Actually, there are sides of this new outfit I haven't shown everyone yet, so I'd be happy if you came to see them.
誕生日たくさんお祝いしてくれてありがとう！ライブも見てくれてありがとう！それではこのあとメンゲンで会おうね。バイバーイ！
Thank you so much for celebrating my birthday! Thank you for watching the live too! Well then, let's meet in the member stream afterwards. Bye-bye!
...